<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News | ChengAo Shen</title>
    <link>https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://chengaoshen.com/media/icon_hu68170e94a17a2a43d6dcb45cf0e8e589_3079_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎉 Graduated from Sichuan Agricultural University</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/graduate_bs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/graduate_bs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The sudden outbreak of the pandemic in 2020 and the delayed college entrance exam caught everyone off guard. As a newly turned adult, I found myself swept along by the tide, ending up in a place I had never imagined: Ya&amp;rsquo;an, Sichuan - Sichuan Agricultural University. With mixed emotions, I boarded a plane to Sichuan for the first time, embarking on my four-year university journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/IMG20221006132316.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;On the flight to Sichuan&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was my first time being so far from home. The Sichuan dialect spoken by my classmates was hard to grasp, and my usual social circle was now out of reach. Additionally, the old dormitories at Sichuan Agricultural University were quite a shock. The antiquated buildings and eight-person rooms without hot water were difficult to adapt to. However, when I knocked on the door of dorm 505, I was greeted by enthusiastic roommates who made me feel a strong sense of belonging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/8E48E868862B2433BE4E9BF4722044C9.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;First-year with roommates&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major of Information and Computational Science was somewhat unfamiliar to me, as I was more focused on computers at the time. I was surprised to find that my first semester courses were all theoretical, like Mathematical Analysis and Advanced Algebra, which caused a lot of discomfort. Fortunately, with the help of teachers and classmates (especially thanks to Chen Huajun), I managed to maintain good grades. I vividly remember burning the midnight oil watching Professor Qiu Weisheng&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV1jR4y1M78W/?vd_source=dfcac4200a17c568f28c0f840ee960b3&#34;&gt;Advanced Algebra&lt;/a&gt; and Professor Chen Jixiu&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV12s411h7v4/?vd_source=dfcac4200a17c568f28c0f840ee960b3&#34;&gt;Mathematical Analysis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/79bfcac481d5d38c5fba2a.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Library where I often studied&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to my interest in microfilms and video production, I met a group of like-minded friends and formed the Ten Cameras club to shoot and produce microfilms. Although we eventually stopped working on projects together for various reasons, I met many genuine friends through this experience. Their influence on my life was significant. This experience taught me that &amp;ldquo;the process is far more important than the result.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/QQ%E5%9B%BE%E7%89%8720210107114933.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ten Cameras group photo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I must mention an unexpected cycling adventure. Initially, I just wanted to repair my bicycle but ended up being taken on a ride to Mount Mengding. Through this event, I met my best friend of four years, Xiao Shiming. His loyalty and enthusiasm left a lasting impression on me. He is one of the purest people I have ever met, always ready to help others. Our friendship is a precious gift from my university years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/1619630790598.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Xiao Shiming&amp;rsquo;s birthday&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the latter part of my university life, I dedicated most of my time to the research lab in preparation for going abroad. I established the &amp;ldquo;Deep Vision Agriculture Lab&amp;rdquo; with fellow undergraduates. In the lab, I met many juniors and participated in various interdisciplinary projects combining biology and artificial intelligence. We applied for various projects like Internet+, College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship, and Research Interest Groups, and published some journal papers. The success of our lab was greatly supported by Professor Shen, who provided us with the necessary resources and guidance. Without him, our lab wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have functioned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/DSC06544.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Lab group photo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During my university years, I encountered many teachers who had a profound impact on me. Among them was Professor Huang Houhui, who taught me Numerical Analysis. His humor and wit left a deep impression on me. Professor Wang Jianjun, who guided me in Mathematical Modeling and Mathematical Analysis, also helped me gain a lot of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/7254d8617bbbdfe2ed970cde721797e4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Photo with teachers, left: Professor Wang Jianjun, right: Professor Huang Houhui&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I want to thank my girlfriend, Mu Siyuan. We met during a research project and fell in love while working together. We share similar values and life philosophies, making her an invaluable partner in my life. She has always been by my side during my research, studies, and leisure time. Without her constant support, I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have achieved any of my accomplishments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/IMG_2545.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;With girlfriend at Chengdu Eastern Memory&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four years have passed in the blink of an eye. To be honest, there were so many moments of reluctance that ended when we took our graduation photos. So, at the end of this blog, please allow me to share some graduation photos to commemorate the past four years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/IMG_4611.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graduation photo with dorm mates&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/DSC06708.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ten Cameras graduation photo (some members)&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/DSC06678.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graduation photo with Xiao&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/DSC06663.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Graduation photo with girlfriend&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ChengAoShen/Image-Hosting/main/images/DSC06790.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The End&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚀 A Brand New Personal Homepage!</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming Fall of 2024, I will be completing my undergraduate studies and beginning my Ph.D. journey. To better present my academic experience and personal information, I have used Hugo to create a new personal homepage (which is the page you are currently viewing)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will continue to update my academic blog and personal news on this homepage. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information about me can be found in &lt;a href=&#34;https://chengaoshen.com/&#34;&gt;Bio&lt;/a&gt;. I sincerely hope my posts can help you. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
