<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News | ChengAo Shen</title>
    <link>https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://chengaoshen.com/media/icon_hu_5e76b9ed60a85934.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/tags/news/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎉 Joined the University of Houston as a PhD student</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/join_uh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/join_uh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, I&amp;rsquo;m starting my PhD journey at the University of Houston. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be part of the UH-D2i-group under the supervision of Professor &lt;a href=&#34;https://nijingchao.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Jingchao Ni&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research focuses on applying machine learning and data science methods for time series prediction and anomaly detection. I am also exploring data science techniques to uncover causal relationships across various fields and develop new methods for causal discovery. Additionally, I am interested in integrating language and vision models through multimodal learning to tackle challenges in time series analysis and causal discovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to working with you all!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚀 A Brand New Personal Homepage!</title>
      <link>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://chengaoshen.com/blogs/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the upcoming Fall of 2024, I will be completing my undergraduate studies and beginning my Ph.D. journey. To better present my academic experience and personal information, I have used Hugo to create a new personal homepage (which is the page you are currently viewing)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will continue to update my academic blog and personal news on this homepage. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More information about me can be found in &lt;a href=&#34;https://chengaoshen.com/&#34;&gt;Bio&lt;/a&gt;. I sincerely hope my posts can help you. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
